Guide to the Richard Pollay. Tobacco industry promotion (TIPS) collection, 1885-2012 and undated RL.11612
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 7000. Corporate Documents, 1923-2004; undated; 10
  - 7008. Smokescreen Documents, 1923-2000; 98
    - Contents of binder--Smoke Screen Documents (Addenda V16b), 1953-1998 (Box 71)
      Includes Karen Miller 1993 thesis: Amplifying the Voice of Business: Hill and Knowlton's Influence on Political, Public, and Media Discourse in Postwar America
    - Contents of binder--Unscientific Perspective of the Tobacco Industry Research Committee, 1923-1998 (Box 71)
      Includes medical journal articles on tobacco and cancer-related issues
  - 7009. CML: The Camel Quarterly, 1999-2001; 99
    - Issues 1,2,5, 1999-2000 (Box 71)
    - The City Edition, 2001 (Box OV1)
  - 7010. Unlimited (Philip Morris/Marlboro), 1996-2003; 100
    - Incomplete run of issues, 1996-2003 (Box OV2)
  - 7011. Philip Morris Magazine, 1987-1992; 101
    - Incomplete run of issues, 1987-1992; 4 folders (Box 71)
    - PM Quarterly, 1991 (Box 71)
  - 7012. Brown and Williamson, 1991; 102
    - Contents of binder--Miscellany, 1991 (Box 71)
      Evidentiary documents from Minnesota litigation
  - 7012.1. Brown and Williamson--Real Edge Magazine, 1999; 103
    - Incomplete run of issues, 1999 (Box 71)
  - 7013. Lorillard, 1978-1981; 104
    - Articles, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
      Includes Kent Anderson, Television Fraud: The History and Implications of Game Show Scandals; memo on age groups of smokers
  - 7014. British American Tobacco, circa 1991-1992; 105
    - Smoking Issues: Claims and Responses, circa 1991-1992 (Box 71)
  - 7999. General Articles About the Tobacco Industry, 1990-2002; undated; 106
    - CBS, 60 Minutes, and the Unseen Interview (Lawrence Grossman), 1996 (Box 71)
    - Cigarette Papers (Jan Weiner), 1996 (Box 71)
    - Smoking Guns: ABC, Philip Morris and the Infamous Apology (Steve Weinberg), 1995 (Box 71)
    - Strategic Response of American Tobacco Companies to Regulatory and Environmental Concerns, circa 1990 (Box 71)
    - Tobacco Industry Statements in the Department of Justice Lawsuit, 2002 (Box 71)
    - Trust Us We're the Tobacco Industry, undated (Box 71)
- 8000. Litigation and Court Records, 1929-2005; undated; 11
  - 8001. Imperial Tobacco/RJR-M v. Attorney General of Canada (Quebec), 1977-2002; undated; 107
    - Attorney General documents V.1, 1978-1986; 3 folders (Box 71)
      AG-08: Export family brand positioning statement; AG-09: Vantage marketing/copy strategy recommendation; AG-10: Vantage "right attitude" advertising text; AG-11: Vantage advertising research
    - Attorney General documents V.2, 1979-1980; 3 folders (Box 71)
      AG-12: Vantage brand positioning statement; AG-13: Export A lassie visits west coast; AG-14: Performance standards
    - Attorney General documents V.3, 1984-1987; 3 folders (Box 72)
      AG-15: Export A brand long-term strategy; AG-16: Third family creative direction recommendation; AG-17: Tempo qualitative post-launch evaluation; AG-18: RJR-MacDonald advertising and promotion spending; AG-21a: Project Viking
    - Attorney General documents V.4, 1986-1988; undated; 3 folders (Box 72)
      AG-21b-c-d: Project Viking; AG-24: Medallion; AG-25: Du Maurier; AG-26: ITL-3 revised
    - Attorney General documents V.5, 1978-1989; 3 folders (Box 72)
      AG-27: Projects Stereo/Phoenix final report; AG-28: Players Light creative development; AG-29: Players strategy; AG-30a: Imperial Tobacco domestic advertising expense; AG-30b: Matinee (Yellow); AG-31: Canada and cigarettes volume; AG-32: Imperial Tobacco media plans; AG-33: Players family working paper
    - Attorney General documents V.6, 1980; 2 folders (Box 72)
      AG-34: 5-year cigarette forecast
    - Attorney General documents V.7, 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 72)
      AG-35: Players Filter '81 creative guidelines; AG-36: F'85 marketing plan; AG-38: Project Twiggy phase 2; AG-40: The LTN (low tar and nicotine) smoking experience; AG-41: Response of the market and of Imperial Tobacco to the smoking and health environment
    - Attorney General documents V.8, 1982; 2 folders (Box OV3)
    - Attorney General documents V.9, 1977-1988; 3 folders (Box 72)
      AG-50; AG-51: The following philosophies have effectively governed ITL's marketing planning and activities; AG-52: Fiscal 1980 marketing objectives; AG-53: Memorandum of agreement between Imperial Tobacco and Royal Canadian Golf Association; AG-54: Exploratory concept research--Matinee print advertising; AG-55: Matinee print ad; AG-56: Medallion 1988; AG-61: Project Day exploratory phase in Edmonton; AG-62: Project Day exploratory phase in Toronto; AG-63: Project Day exploratory phase in Edmonton DA2; AG-216: Project 16 (English youth); AG-217: Project 16
    - Attorney General documents V.10, 1982-1986; 2 folders (Box 72)
      AG-220: Project Stereo advertising evaluation; AG-222: Export family strategy document
    - Catalog of corporate documents, undated (Box 72)
    - Cigarette market strategy research (RJR-186), 1982 (Box 72)
    - Contents of binder--Articles and appeal documents, 1994-2002; 2 folders (Box 72)
      Includes: RJR-MacDonald Inc. v. Canada (A.G.)--Reflections from the perspective of health (Rob Cunningham); Supreme Court of Canada appeal documents; Expert reports "How Cigarette Advertising Works: Rich Imagery and Poor Information" and "The Role of Packaging seen through Industry Documents (Richard Pollay)
    - Contents of binder--Expert opinions, 1989; 2 folders (Box 72)
      Testimony from J. Allen Best, Joel Cohen, John Jenkins, Katherine Covell, Leonard Reid, Michael Chandler, Michael Waterson, Richard Pollay, William Leiss
    - Contents of binder--Expert opinions, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Contents of binder--Functions and Management of Cigarette Advertising (Richard Pollay), 1989; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Contents of binder--Selected court documents, 1977-1988; 4 folders (Box 73)
      AG-21b: Project Viking v.2 an attitudinal model of smoking; AG-21c: Project Viking v.3 product issues; AG-21d: Project Viking wave 2; AG-216: Project 16 (English youth); AG-217: Project Plus/Minus (juvenile smoking); RJR-6: Youth 1987
    - Contents of binder--Summary arguments/Memoire d'argumentation, 1990; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1992-1995 (Box 73)
    - Court transcript v.54, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Court transcript v.55, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Court transcript v.56, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Export family marketing strategy (RJR-174), undated (Box 73)
    - Fiscal '80 media plans (ITL-13), undated (Box 73)
    - Judgment, Court of Appeals--Tobacco Products Control Act, 1993 (Box 73)
    - List of exhibits, undated (Box 73)
    - MacDonald Tobacco corporate goals and objectives (RJR-185), undated (Box 73)
    - Mémoire d'argumentation du Procureur Général du Canada (Summary argument), 1990; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Project Stereo advertising evaluation (AG-027), 1986 (Box 73)
    - Project Stereo Phoenix management presentation, undated (Box 73)
    - Research dimensions document for Vantage (RJR-189), 1979 (Box 73)
    - RJR-M brand family and smoker segmentation study (RJR-175), 1986 (Box 73)
    - RJR-M young adult study (RJR-7), 1987 (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Appeal document, 1994; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Index General, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 6, 1994; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 7, 1994; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 8, 1994; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 9, 1994; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 10, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 11, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 12, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 12, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Supreme Court of Canada/Appeal--Factum--Annex--Volume 13, 1994; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Tobacco Products Control Act exhibits in AG of Canada v. ITL, 1991 (Box 75)
    - Vantage family 1983-1987 strategic plan; 1983 operating plan (RJR-178), 1982 (Box 75)
    - Vantage usage and attitude study (RJR-176), 1983; 2 folders (Box 75)
  - 8002. Cipollone v. Liggett Group, 1929-1990; undated; 108
    - Article--Cigarette Advertising Regulation Today: Unintended Consequences and Missed Opportunities? (John Calfee), undated (Box 76)
    - Article--Cigarette Wars, undated (Box OV3)
    - Article--Cigarettes and Health: A Legal Analysis (Richard Wegman), 1966 (Box 76)
    - Article--Embattled Tobacco's New Strategy, 1963 (Box OV3)
    - Article--Ghost of Cigarette Advertising Past (John Calfee), 1986 (Box 76)
    - Article--History of Smokeless Tobacco in the United States (Arden Christian and Elbert Glover), 1987 (Box 76)
    - Article--Mixed Messages for Women: A social history of cigarette smoking and advertising (Virginia Ernster), 1985 (Box 76)
    - Article--Tobacco Industry Response to Public Health Concern: A Content Analysis of Cigarette Ads (Kenneth Warner), 1985 (Box 76)
    - Brief for Petitioner (U.S. Supreme Court), 1990 (Box 76)
    - Chronologies, 1965-1981 (Box 76)
      Chronological timelines relating to anti-smoking campaigns, the Federal Communications Commission, Federal Trade Commission, government intervention in smoking and health controversy and lung cancer
    - Cipollone smoking history, undated (Box 76)
      Dates of brand choice, responses to advertising and health warnings 1941-1970s
    - Comments on evidentiary exhibits and documents, undated (Box 76)
    - Confidential documents, 1967-1977 (Box 76)
    - Congressional appeal to FTC regarding cigarette advertising, 1979 (Box 76)
    - Contents of binder, 1932-1990 (Box 76)
      Richard Pollay articles, miscellaneous data on smoking, clippings
    - Depositions--Antonio Cipollone, 1985; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Claude Martin, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Domenica Cilento, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Harold Kassarjian, 1987; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Richard Pollay, 1987; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Richard Pollay--Exhibit Books vols. 1-4, 1990; 6 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Roger Blackwell, 1987; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Depositions--Rose Cipollone, 1984 (Box 77)
    - Depositions--Seymour Sudman, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Depositions--Thomas De Francesco, 1985; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Depositions--Thomasina Deyglio, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Direct examinations, 1984-1987 (Box 77)
      Testimony from Antonio Cipollone, Domenica Cilento, Thomas De Francesco, Thomasina Deyglio
    - Expert witnesses, circa 1987 (Box 77)
      Includes Benjamin Klein, Claude Martin, Dexter Neadle, Harold Kassarjian, Richard Pollay, Robert Blackwell, Seymour Sudman
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1954-1980 (Box 77)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)--Docket No. 6077 briefs and order, 1953-1958 (Box 77)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)--Report: Consumer Beliefs and Behavior with Respect to Cigarette Smoking (Martin Fishbein), 1977 (Box 77)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)--Review of the Nature and Extent of Cigarette Advertising in the United States (Robert Hutchings), 1981 (Box 77)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)--Staff report on FTC cigarette advertising investigation, 1981 (Box 77)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)--Working Paper: Cigarette Advertising, Health Information and Regulation before 1970 (John Calfee), 1985 (Box 77)
    - Highlights: Chronology of cigarette advertising and health claims 1928-1987, circa 1988 (Box 77)
    - Historical notes (clippings on history of cigarette advertising 1920s-1980s), 1929-1987; 7 folders (Box 77)
    - Historical notes (clippings on history of cigarette advertising 1920s-1980s), 1941-1986 (Box OV3)
    - Jury charge, interrogatories, circa 1990 (Box 77)
    - JWT Archives (research notes, photocopies), 1963; undated (Box 77)
    - Major opinion summary, undated (Box 77)
    - National Association of Broadcasters (NAB)--Voluntary cigarette advertising code, 1964-1968 (Box 77)
    - Opinion of Judge Sarokin, 1989 (Box 77)
    - Philip Morris, 1970-1974 (Box 77)
      Includes timeline of "tar derby," marketing research, material on Parliament and Virginia Slims cigarette packaging and promotion
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Loose documents, 1934-1974; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 1700, 1971 (Box 77)
      Cigarette Market presentation prepared for Lorillard
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 1701-1704, 1972-1973 (Box 77)
      1701: Consumer reaction to proposed concepts for True cigarettes; 1702: True cigarette concept test; 1703: Brand image research for Lorillard; 1704: Summary and implications of Monitor presentation (social values and consumer behavior)
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 1705-1710, 1974-1975 (Box 77)
      1705: Monitor presentation; 1706: Summary of True focus group oral report; 1707: Filter cigarette smokers' attitudes toward Super Hi-Fi cigarettes and their perceptions of True; 1708: Super Hi-Fi strategy recommendations; 1709: True marketing and copy strategy; 1710: Cigarette advertising presentation for Lorillard/Loews Theatres
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 1721-1724, 1976-1981 (Box 77)
      1721: Super Hi-Fi cigarette opportunity and situation analysis; 1722: True strategies; 1723: Consumer smoking patterns, effects of government reports; 1724: Research on factors effecting cigarette usage
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2000-2003, 1950-1958 (Box 77)
      Gallup poll questions on smoking and health opinions; research on physician smoking habits and attitudes; smoking and cardiovascular disease
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2004-2005a, 1959; undated (Box 77)
      2004: Roper study on smoking and kinds of cigarettes; 2005: Philip Morris memo on Roper study; 2005A: Doctors and Smoking
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2006-2008, 1960-1964 (Box 77)
      2006: Tobacco Institute study on doctors' attitudes toward tobacco and health; 2007: Minutes of Tobacco Institute Public Relations Committee meeting; JWT report to Liggett & Myers on advertising impact and consumer attitude;2008: Hill & Knowlton study of impact of Surgeon General reports
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2009-2016, 1966-1972 (Box 78)
      2009: Tobacco Institute poll on smoking attitudes; 2009a: Memo from Edwin Finch (President, Brown & Williamson) to Sen. Earle Clements (President, Tobacco Institute) about warning labels on cigarette packages; 2010: Memo from John Kraft to Sen. Clements concerning a smoking attitude study; 2011: Hooper research report on smoking attitudes; 2012-2013: Memos from Rosser Reeves (Tiderock) to Sen. Clements concerning a Ted Bates telephone survey on smoking attitudes; 2014: Memo from David Loomis (Ted Bates) to Reginald Wells (Tiderock) summarizing smoking research; 2015: Gallup poll on smoking and health; 2016: Roper study of public attitudes toward smoking and the tobacco industry
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2017-2018, 1976 (Box 78)
      2017: Highlights from smoking and health survey; 2018: Gallup poll on cigarette smoking
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2019, 1969; 6 folders (Box 78)
      2019: U.S. Public Health Service study "Use of Tobacco"
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2100-2202, 1960-1975 (Box 78)
      2100: Memo from W.C. Hoyt to Dr. C.C. Little regarding the American Cancer Society; 2101: Domestic cigarette advertising expenditures; 2200-2202: Philip Morris summaries of smoking surveys
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2307, 1957; 2 folders (Box 78)
      2307: Motivational survey for Liggett & Myers
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered 2800-2822, 1967-1968 (Box 78)
      Documents relating to True Magazine, National Enquirer articles about smoking and health, cancer
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered P2-P7, 1968-1970 (Box 78)
      P2: Philip Morris report on consumer promotion offer; P4: Philip Morris Virginia Slims consumer study; P5-P7: Philip Morris summaries of telephone surveys
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered P8-P11, 1968-1970 (Box 78)
      P8: Philip Morris summaries of telephone surveys; P9-P11: Philip Morris cigarette tracking research
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered P12-P16, 1970-1972 (Box 78)
      P12-P16: Philip Morris cigarette tracking research
    - Plaintiff exhibits--Numbered P20-P24, 1968-1973 (Box 78)
      Documents relating to Virginia Slims marketing
    - Protective Order, 1986 (Box 78)
    - Richard Pollay articles and presentations, backup file, 1987; undated (Box 78)
    - Richard Pollay expert witness, 1987-1988 (Box 78)
    - Richard Pollay radio cigarette commercials tape log, undated (Box 78)
      Cassettes RL-11612-CAS-021 and RL11612-CAS-022 removed to Audiovisual Materials Box AV-13
    - Silva Thins advertisement "Here's Another Good Reason Why I'm a Thinner", undated (Box 78)
    - Slater/Altman study: Cigarette Advertising Strategies, 1960-1985: Trends and Themes for Youth, Women and General Audiences, 1987 (Box 78)
      Michael Slater, David Altman, Cheryl Albright, Nathan Maccoby; Stanford University Institute for Communication Research
    - Summary of trial testimony, circa 1988 (Box 78)
    - Tobacco Industry Research Committee (TIRC) background memorandum for press, radio and tv, and special writers, 1955 (Box 78)
    - Tobacco Institute, 1959-1974 (Box 78)
    - Tobacco Institute fan mail, 1970; undated (Box 78)
    - Tobacco Products Liability Project press release, 1988 (Box 78)
      "Incriminating Cigarette Industry Documents Released"
    - Tobacco Products Litigation Reporter, 1988 March (Box 78)
    - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1988; 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1988; 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Transcripts of Proceedings--Summary, undated (Box 79)
    - Trial brief--Liggett Group, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Trial brief--Lorillard, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Trial brief--Philip Morris, 1987 (Box 79)
    - True cigarette print advertising, 1974-1975 (Box 79)
  - 8003. Allgood v. R.J. Reynolds, American Tobacco Company, 1930s-1996; 109
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993-1996 (Box 80)
    - Discovery materials, 1953-1962 (Box 80)
    - Notes on advertising documents acquired, undated (Box OV3)
    - Plaintiffs' memorandum, 1994 (Box 80)
    - Protective Order, 1992 (Box 80)
    - Richard Pollay declarations in opposition to defendant motion for summary judgment, 1993; 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Advertising materials, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Advertising materials, 1930s-1950s; 19 folders (Box 81)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12A, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 81)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12B, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12C, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 82)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12D, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12E, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12F, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12F, 1930s-1950s (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12G, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12H, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12I, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12J, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12K, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12L, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12M, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12N, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12O, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12P, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12Q, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12R, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12S, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12S, 1930s-1950s (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12T, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12U, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12V, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12W, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12X, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 85)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12X, 1930s-1950s (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12Y, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12Z, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12CC, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12DD, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12EE, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12FF, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12FF, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12II, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12JJ, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12LL, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12MM, 1930s-1950s; 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12NN, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12NN, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12OO, 1930s-1950s; 5 folders (Box 88)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12PP, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--12QQ, 1930s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Documents produced pursuant to Plaintiffs' request re: Advertising--Unnumbered, 1930s-1950s; 3 folders (Box 88)
  - 8004. Lerardi v. Lorillard, 1952-1993; 110
    - Contents of binder, 1952-1993; 3 folders (Box 88)